{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is output for −\na = ['he', 'she', 'we']\n' '.join(a)?",
      "answers": [
        "['heshewe']",
        "'heshewe'",
        "['he she we']",
        "'he she we'"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is false statement in python",
      "answers": [
        "int(144)==144",
        "int('144')==144",
        "int(144.0)==144",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "In the following options which are python libraries which are used for data analysis and scientific computations",
      "answers": [
        "Numpy",
        "Scipy",
        "Pandas",
        "All The Above"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is output of following −\nprint('any'.encode())",
      "answers": [
        "'any'",
        "‘yan’",
        "b’any’",
        "x’any’"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which options are correct to create an empty set in Python?",
      "answers": [
        "{}",
        "()",
        "[]",
        "set()"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Select the correct function among them which can be used to write the data to perform for a binary output?",
      "answers": [
        "Write",
        "Output.binary",
        "Dump",
        "Binary.output"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the output of print(2%6)",
      "answers": [
        "ValueError",
        "0.33",
        "2",
        "2/6"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How far is the moon from Earth?",
      "answers": [
        "7,918 miles (12,742 km)",
        "86,881 miles (139,822 km)",
        "238,400 miles (384,400 km)",
        "35,980,000 miles (57,910,000 km)"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 65 times 52?",
      "answers": [
        "117",
        "3120",
        "3380",
        "3520"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "How tall is Mount Everest?",
      "answers": [
        "6,683 ft (2,037 m)",
        "7,918 ft (2,413 m)",
        "19,341 ft (5,895 m)",
        "29,029 ft (8,847 m)"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "When did The Avengers come out?",
      "answers": [
        "May 2, 2008",
        "May 4, 2012",
        "May 3, 2013",
        "April 4, 2014"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 48,879 in hexidecimal?",
      "answers": [
        "0x18C1",
        "0xBEEF",
        "0xDEAD",
        "0x12D591"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    }
  ]
}